

## Profile

Highly motivated and academically accomplished student with a strong commitment to learning and contributing to the advancement of knowledge in the field. Distinctive skills are: diligence, perseverance, curiosity, sociability. I have experience working with the following technology stack: C/C++, Python, Java, Qt, Android development.

# Employment Experience

Resident of the IT-Academy at "НЕЙМАРК", Nizhniy Novgorod

September 2022 — Present

Work with talented young people in Russia, helping to solve cases of leading companies. Over the course of several days, participants solve cases such as: olympiad programming, app development.

One of my team won in the latter category, to implement with my support an application for analysing the amount of lactate in the blood with a graph of the dependence of lactic acid salts in the blood on the time of physical activity: click. The patient was measured periodically (every 10 minutes during an hour of gym, for example). At the end of the measurements, the program interpolate the data and plot the function with the calculated intermediate values, find the intersection points of curves and the minimum distance between them.

# Private tutor for the Unified State Exam, Nizhniy Novgorod

September 2022 — Present

Prepare high school students (grades 10-11) for the Unified State Exam in specialized mathematics and computer science. Prepared more than 18 students. Topics covered were: interpolation, systems of nonlinear equations, convex polygons and their intersection areas, algorithms, data structures.

## Pet projects

2022 — Present

- Smart voice assistant for the driver (Flet, Python, Pandas): click
- Intersection area calculator for convex polygons (Qt, C++): click
- Mobile messenger application (Android, Firebase, Java): click
- Interpolation with cubic splines (Gnuplot, C): click

## Education

Technical Lyceum #38, Nizhniy Novgorod

September 2019 — June 2022

**HSE University, Nizhniy Novgorod** 

September 2022 — Present

Applied Mathematics and Information Science

#### **Details**

Nizhniy Novgorod Russian Federation +79308106722 pddMas@mail.ru

Date of birth 10.11.2003

#### Links

GitHub Telegram VK

#### **Skills**

Communication

Creativity

Adaptability

Fast Learner

**Time Management** 

Teamwork

#### Languages

Russian

**English** 

#### **Hobbies**

- Application development
- Tutoring (maths and informatics, Unified State Exam)
- Mathematics
- Squash and judo

## **★** Courses and Achievements

## Samsung IT-School, Mobile development, Nizhniy Novgorod

September 2019 — June 2020

The course covered the basics of mobile application development for the Android platform, Java fundamentals, OOP, algorithms and data structures. My graduation project was a messenger in conjunction with Firebase Cloud Storage, which won first place in the regional round of the project competition: click.

# All-Russian Al Hackathon "Digital Breakthrough", Nizhniy Novgorod

September 2023

Developed a GUI application for an intelligent driver assistant in Python in conjunction with Flet. The advantages of this solution are: cross-platform, simple and clear architecture with beautiful interfaces, the ability to quickly deploy the application, built-in web server: click and click.